Good afternoon, Badminton!
JASUN TV!
What are we doing today?
Today, we're going to...
What's wrong with you?
We want to be the green girl.
What?
Not a wall, but a girl.
First, let's watch this video.
What's wrong with you?
Today, we're going to...
Thank you for coming to the invitation
of Tokimeki for the 2020 Tokidoki
Christmas Party.
I am Hito-chan,★
Please don't make a loud voice on the
outside.
Look forward to my high-tech sound
saver..
Please click the good button.
I am Hitocha, the super red character.
I'm Oharu from Tokimeki MINK.
I'm Haruka Koizumi.
Thank you for watching!
Hey Ao! Don't be so flustered!
Isn't it a bit too much?
What is a handshake?
I get nervous before a live.
I get nervous and I can't read the
handwriting.
I can't say anything about your hair.
The live has started since we entered
the venue.
So, we are going to focus on it.
Today's topic is...
We are going to improve our narration
skills!
We are going to improve it!
Today, we have a special guest.
Let's get started.
Thank you for coming!
Hello!
I'm Shigeki Kiyono.
Kiyona is a top runner in the
commentators who are not known in pro
wrestling and martial arts.
She is a commentator who makes
commentating into a Japanese game.
This time, we have invited Kiyona
Shigeki, a freelance announcer.
I would like you to train our
vocabulary.
Thank you very much.
It's a very friendly introduction.
Did you remember this?
I was the most nervous in the past.
I did.
You are amazing.
I can't help but watch the video.
I can't help but watch it.
It's terrible.
Why did it become like that?
Why?
Who did you hear it from?
I heard it from someone.
Maybe fans like it when you read it in
a fun way.
But it's an important point.
We have to listen to it.
It's important to read it and convey it
to the other person.
You have to convey it.
I've been an announcer for 25 or 26
years.
I think I'm doing better than you.
Not a little.
I've been doing this job since I was
born.
I want to teach you how to use it.
Thank you.
Are you motivated?
Yes.
Are you really motivated?
I'll be strict.
I'll do my best.
Let's study announcer skills together
today.
Learn the key points of the prediction!
Study with your mosque!
This program is a program where six
people who work to promote something
exciting
and challenge various things to improve
the excitement barometer in the world.
So, Kiyama-san, what do you teach
first?
First of all, let's start with reading
the manuscript.
You saw it in the VTR.
Reading the manuscript is one of the
important things.
The important thing is to read it one
by one and then convey it to the other
party.
So, even if you read it without any
mistakes, it doesn't mean anything if
you don't convey it.
I have a manuscript of the live
performance, so I will read it as a
model.
Thank you for coming to the invitation
of the Super Exciting Advertising Club's
Doki Doki Christmas Party 2020.
Before the conference, I would like to
ask the audience to be careful.
I strongly refuse to take pictures,
record, and record in the venue during
the performance.
No loud voices in the venue, no
excessive jumps.
Please enjoy with applause, hand
gestures, and penlight.
Please cooperate with the staff to
evacuate if necessary.
Then, the conference will begin soon.
I would like each member to read this.
Do you usually read it separately?
Yes, I listen to it several times per
live.
So, today I will read it alone.
There is no other person to rely on.
By the way, it is not the new record of
Doki Doki Christmas Party 2020 that you
read.
I prepared a manuscript here at random.
It's the same as the live performance.
It's the same as the live performance,
and when I went to the venue, I was
given a manuscript.
I was given a manuscript.
This is also in our world.
Suddenly, I was handed over on the spot
and I was completely unprepared.
What is important at that time is a
little advanced technique.
When you are speaking, you are speaking
while following the line you are
reading.
The eyes are already on the next line.
I'm not sure.
That's why the announcer is wrong.
Please think that it is the same as the
musical style of the instrument when
playing.
We are doing what we are already
chasing the next while playing.
This is a little advanced technique,
but if you have time, please speak out
and look ahead.
Thank you.
Let's get started!
Let's start with Tsujino.
I'm nervous.
I was nervous.
My stomach hurts already.
Another day, the surprise party
continued.
Yes.
Then, let's try to read the manuscript.
I will judge whether the contents of
the manuscript were clearly conveyed.
I will decide whether you passed or
not.
I think you will be nervous.
Kaori, do your best!
Do your best!
Then, Sugino, please.
Yes.
Then, I will start.
The 7th issue of the new photo album is
on sale!
The 7th issue of the new series of the
Super Exciting Advertisement is on sale!
The Valentine's Day-only photos are on
sale!
The 7th issue of the new series of the
Super Exciting Advertisement is on sale!
It is possible that tofu is used in the
advertisement.
In addition, the number of times it
will be released...
The product that sold a lot and became
a super price
For the super excitement advertisement
The standard T-shirt muffler towel has
been re-imported
Speaking of super excitement
advertisement, this
By all means, how about with the name
photo?
This
Yes, Mr. Tsujino read it
It's difficult
It's all so difficult.
I don't want to!
Now, I will announce the judges for
Tsujino.
Let's see if Tsujino has understood.
The judges are...
Really?
I thought it was the last one.
I saw the mark of X.
I was only going to press X.
I think it's a bit...
I think it's a bit of a shame that
we're watching this for the first time.
First, it says, start selling.
Tsujino, this is all about selling.
And then, the Valentine's Day special
shot.
This is the meaning of one.
You have to read this at once.
Where to divide it or keep it alone.
I think about the meaning of the
sentence.
I don't think it's weird to cut it
here.
And then, one group of five.
One group of five.
It's an intonation.
Five?
Five.
One, two, three, four, five.
Five?
Five.
It's difficult.
And, it's a random word.
It's a word for a milk.
Yes, it is.
And, it's a word for a sale.
It's not that you can't read it wrong,
but if you add up all the words, it's
not clear.
Unfortunately, you have to pass this
test.
It's difficult.
Thank you.
Next, An-san.
Let's go.
The official fan club of the Super
Tokimeki Anniversary Club, which will be
held in 2021, has been opened on
February 15th.
The fan club has a lot of member
benefits, so I will guide you below.
Membership limited ticket selection and
event tickets, gallery content that
delivers pictures of the live and event,
and fan club-only video.
Daily exchange diary of members updated
at 6 pm, one word from the members that
will be the source of energy for a week
updated every Monday morning 6 o'clock,
individual contents of each member
updated by day, staff report that
delivers a behind-the-scenes story of
the Tokimeki episode updated every
Wednesday,
In addition, there are mail magazines
that deliver gift plans and latest
information, and wonderful gift benefits
for birthdays and people in various
regions.
For more information, please check the
official fan club website.
We look forward to your participation
in this opportunity.
Wow!
It was a great day!
I was talking all the time.
I was nervous.
Now, let's talk about Ann's reading of
the manuscript.
Ann's reading of the manuscript is...
correct!
Wow!
I read it smoothly.
This is a good reading of Tsujino-san.
I read it well.
It's a good reading, isn't it? I was
surprised that I could read it so
smoothly at first glance.
Yes!
I was able to convey it by listening.
Especially, the introduction of the
manuscript and the fan club were very
good.
I was able to convey it well.
There were also many words that were
out of place.
February 15th.
The correct accent was February.
But, even if there are some mistakes,
the result is consistent, so it's a good
score.
Did you notice the original script
while reading it?
A little bit.
But, when I'm always working on
something, I usually notice the next
one.
You're good at it.
It's cool.
The winner is Ogami, the second place.
Thank you.
Let's start with Sakai.
I'll do my best.
It's hard to follow the junior.
Now, Sakai's challenge.
Please start.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for coming to the invitation
of the super exciting Christmas party
2020 from Tokimeki.
I'm Hitoka Sakai.
Before I start, I would like to ask you
to be careful.
I strongly refuse to take pictures,
record, and record in the venue during
the performance.
Today, guests who are not seated on the
second floor cannot watch even if they
stand up.
No cheering, loud voices, or jumping
corners in the venue.
Please enjoy with applause, hand-claps,
and penlights.
Please note that the actions that cause
inconvenience to the guests around you
are prohibited.
If you are in an emergency, please
evacuate according to the instructions
of the staff.
I'll be back soon.
Please wait for me.
It was Sakai's challenge.
I would like to evaluate Sakai's
reading of the manuscript.
Sakai's reading of the manuscript is...
What?
I was reading it, but I felt that I was
reading the manuscript too much.
I felt that my feelings were going to
my hair.
I think it's better to read it and put
it out to the other person.
I think it's better to convey the
feeling to the other person.
I feel like I'm just looking at my
hair.
Sometimes I change my words.
I'm asking for your cooperation.
I'm changing my words.
But I'm not waiting for you at the end.
Thank you.
That's all.
Unfortunately, you failed.
Next, let's move on to Koizumi.
ающらしい
years
This is Mr. Izumi Ko's manuscript
reading
Dango is a type of sweet that is eaten
in various seasons, such as Hanami in
spring, Omatsuri in summer, and Otsukimi
in autumn.
It is said that this dango was
recognized as a snack in the Heian
period.
At that time, there were other
processed sweets such as soy bean mochi,
azuki mochi, and senbei.
Dango is still loved by people even
though the times have changed.
The traditional taste that has been
around for a long time has not changed.
There are many popular stores in
Shimizu that continue to inherit the
taste in Tokyo.
Even if it doesn't look flashy, the
feelings that are contained in one dango
are the best sweet that heals the hearts
of those who eat it.
In order to continue to give people
that impression, Japanese dango
craftsmen will continue to make
delicious dango every day.
Wait, this is...
Thank you for your hard work, Koizumi-
san.
Please return to your seat.
I want to eat dango.
It was hot, Haru.
What kind of dango is this?
I don't know.
Then, it is a judgment against Koizumi-
san's manuscript.
Koizumi-san's manuscript reading is
this.
It is correct.
Great!
It was a long manuscript, but you were
able to read it well.
I was sweating a lot.
Were you surprised?
I was surprised. The content was too
difficult.
It's quite difficult, isn't it?
Like soybean mochi or azuki mochi.
I was able to read the kanji well.
Like senbei.
Great.
But I didn't feel like I was drinking a
lot of good things.
I was able to read it well.
I was laughing at the delicious
dumpling at the end.
I was wondering what kind of program it
was.
But you were able to read it well.
Thank you very much.
You have passed the test.
Set 1
Here's Mr. Suda's results.
The 7th issue of the new photo album is
now on sale!
There are so many photos that you can't
miss this time!
There are 5 photos in one set.
There are random photos of the members'
autographs.
In addition, the T-shirt and muffler
towel for the super-exciting
advertisement section, which was sold
out before the release, have been re-
introduced.
How about taking a picture with this
advertisement?
Thank you very much.
Please return to your seat.
She read the advertisement.
The judgment of reading the
advertisement is...
I'm sorry.
She read the advertisement with all her
might.
I'm sorry.
She is crying.
What's wrong?
Let's make it a big one.
Isn't it normal?
I'm sorry.
I think I read it.
Can you cry?
Please subscribe to this channel.
I was scared when the bugs came out.
How scary was it today?
Why?
It's okay. I'm a person who can say a
lot.
But it was transmitted that you were
reading hard.
The main character is a senior.
When you get on, you can get a turn
naturally.
You can also get a strong and weak.
I want to recommend this feeling.
How is it?
I think you can read it with that
feeling.
Yoshikawa-san, please.
Lastly, Yoshikawa-san, please.
Please.
We've all seen it.
We've heard the most common points.
I think I can say something.
The last question.
Please read the manuscript of
Yoshikawa-san.
Yes.
The last question.
In spring, we eat flowers, in summer,
we eat matsuri, and in the month of the
moon, we eat dango, a seasonal snack.
Dango was recognized as a snack in the
Heian period.
At that time, we ate other things like
daizumochi and omamemochi.
We ate senbei and other snacks.
Even though the times have changed, we
still love dango.
The traditional taste of dango has not
changed.
The taste of dango will continue in
Tokyo.
There are many popular places in
Shinisei that continue to promote dango.
Even if it doesn't look flashy, the
feelings buried in that dango are the
best
The best feeling to heal the heart of
the eater
In order to continue to give that
impression to people in the future,
Japanese dango craftsmen continue to
make delicious dango every day.
Yoshikawa-san read the manuscript.
Please read it.
Dango!
It's a bean cake.
Why didn't you say it?
I shouldn't have said it.
What's a bean cake?
I heard it for the first time.
It might be delicious, so it's a bean
cake.
Here is the evaluation of Yoshikawa-
san's reading of the manuscript.
It's a little misread.
It's a bean cake.
Then, the phenomenon.
And the thought that was praised.
The thought that was praised?
The thought that was praised.
Oh, I see.
But you were reading it quite slowly.
Isn't that bad?
I'm reading it slowly, and I'm
listening without thinking.
There was a little mistake.
That mistake was unnecessary.
This is bad.
But anyway, the word dumpling has been
mentioned many times.
It's a story about dumplings.
We will continue to tell you about
dumplings.
If you read it wrong, you can say,
I'm sorry.
And then you can go back to the
original.
Then you can correct it.
And people who listen to it will know
that you made a mistake.
It's common in our world.
If you make a mistake, you can say, I'm
sorry.
Please use it.
That's all for today.
This was a challenge to read the
manuscript.
If you want to try narration,
If you are looking forward to the next
live,
Please like and subscribe to our
channel!
See you next time!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I remember the time we met
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I play the sound of rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I play the sound of rain drops
I play the rainbow piano